Stafford, Ronald B.; Papers apap217
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislation, 1974-2002; 9; 32.51 cubic ft.
  - Legislative Resolution, R. Gordon Fort Ann's Man of the Year Award, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 107)
  - Legislative Resolution, Retirement of Dr. Blank of Adirondack Community College, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 108)
  - Legislative Resolution, 25th Anniversary of Community Workshop Inc., 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 109)
  - Legislative Resolution, 75th Anniversary of Camp Chingachgook, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 110)
  - Authorize the Olympic Regional Development Authority to Mortgage its Real Property, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 111)
  - Amend Section 20 of the General Construction Law, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 112)
  - Extend Family Court Jurisdiction to All Matrimonial Actions and Proceedings, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 113)
  - Clarifies the Definition of "Financial Intermediary", 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 114)
  - Transfer Maintenance of Certain State Highways to St. Lawrence County, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 115)
  - Evaluate the Economic Impact of the Proposed United States-Canada Trade Agreement, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 116)
  - Grant Retirement Credit to State Police Officers who Served in the Armed Forces, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 117)
  - Considers "True Leases" and "Finance Leases" as a Lease of Personal Property, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 118)
  - Authorize Payment of Transportation Aid to Salem Central School District, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 119)
  - Establishment of the Kingsbury Water District No. 2, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 120)
  - Permit the New York State Urban Development Corporation to Assist in Financing the New York Gear, Inc. Land Use Improvement Project, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 121)
  - Permit Banking Organizations to Invest Notes and Bonds Secured by Junior Mortgage on Condominium Unites, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 122)
  - Establish a Uniform Fee for Filings with County Clerks, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 123)
  - Allow Fees Paid by Licensed Guides to be Proportionately Refunded, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 124)
  - Reimburse Counties for Full Time DAs Mandated Salary Increase, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 125)
  - Create a Civil Service Commission within the Judiciary, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 126)
  - Permit Qualified Psychologists or Psychiatrists to Serve as Psychiatric Examiners During a Trial, 1988 (Box 18 (9-Legislation), Folder 127)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Rights Law, in Relation to Liability for Acts of Persons Assisting Police Officers, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - Allowing Counties the Option to Pay Bounty on the Taking of Coyotes, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - Permit Judges and Justices who Served at Least Six Years to Solemnize Marriages, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - Abolish the County Court by Merging it with Supreme Court, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 4)
  - Provide the Town of Whitehall with the Amount Needed to Operate and Maintain State-Mandated Sewage Treatment Works, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - Procedures for Determining Gubernatorial Inability and Filing a Vacancy in the Office of the Lieutenant Governor, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - Jurisdictional Realignments in the State Highway System, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - Lighting Districts Assessed by Ad Valorem or Benefit Basis, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - Permit the Creation of a "Springing" Power of Attorney, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 9)
  - Increase Costs Awards in Courts of Limited Jurisdiction, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - Appropriation for Washington County Sewer District #2, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - An Act to Amend the Civil Practice Law and Rules, in Relation to the Rate of Interest on Judgments, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - Prohibits the DEC and APA from Designating Land as Freshwater Wetland if it doesn't Appear on a Map Filed with the County Clerk, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - Enforcement of Consent Orders on Landfills, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - Land Sellers must Notify Prospective Buyers of any Hazardous Waste, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - Authorize Altering the Woodland Environment to Improve Wildlife, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 16)
  - State Highways Stay Open if Town has been Maintaining them, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - Deficiency Appropriation for the Judiciary, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 18)
  - Eminent Domain Procedure Law Applies to New York City, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - Reduce the amount of State Mandates on local governments, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - Creation the Essex County Solid Waste Management Authority and Providing for its Functions, Powers and Duties, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - Funds to the DEC for Upgrading and Rehabilitating all the State's Fish Hatcheries and Facilities, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - Authorize the DEC to Reconstruct the Lester Flow Dam, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - Three Year Budget, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 24)
  - New York State can Purchase Land to Establish Forest Management Areas, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 25)
  - Amendments to the Uniform City Court Act, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 26)
  - Permit Incumbent Judges in Elective Positions to Seek Reelection, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 27)
  - Merge New York State Major Trial Courts into the Supreme Court, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 28)
  - Year Round Open Coyote Hunting Season, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 29)
  - Amend the Surrogate's Court Procedure Act, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 30)
  - Establishment of an Ethics Issues Advisory Board for Judges, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 31)
  - Allow Dead Wood to be Gathered from floor of State-Owned Forest Land, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 32)
  - Prevent Already Existing Man-Made Structures in the Adirondack Parks from Being Destroyed, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 33)
  - Creating a Common Retirement Fund Board of Trustees, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 34)
  - Jurisdiction of Family Court, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 35)
  - Allow a Municipality to Veto the Proposed Site Chosen by a Regional OTB Corporation, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 36)
  - Landlord Responsibilities After a Tenant's Wrongful Abandonment, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 37)
  - Definition of "a state rate of interest", 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 38)
  - Issuing a Free Fishing License to People who are Severely Disabled, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 39)
  - Records of Attorneys' Names at the Court of Appeals, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 40)
  - Reimburse Localities for Sewage Treatment Facilities Construction, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 41)
  - Recognize the 150th Anniversary of the Adirondack Park and Assist Education Activities Relating to it, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 42)
  - Payment of Bonuses to Korean and Vietnam Veterans, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 43)
  - Descent and Distribution Laws, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 44)
  - Legislative Resolution Commemorating the 30th Anniversary of the Fort Edward Rescue Squad Auxiliary, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 45)
  - Transfer of the Responsibilities of the Lake Champlain Bridge Commission, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 46)
  - Extend the Jurisdiction of Surrogate's Court, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 47)
  - Jurisdiction of County Court, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 48)
  - Authorizing the use of Floridone to Eradicate Aquatic Weed Growth, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 49)
  - Rights of Nonmarital Children Under Wills and Other Instruments, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 50)
  - Establish Method of Payment of Contingent Fees for Attorneys, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 51)
  - Authorize the Courts to Approve Structured Settlements when Requested by Settling Parties, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 52)
  - Grants Certain Powers to Special Agents of the US Department of Commerce, Office of Export Enforcement, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 53)
  - Challenging a Juror, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 54)
  - Amends the Uniform Gift to Minors Act and Payments to Conservators, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 55)
  - Establish a Public Benefit Corporation to Implement a Solid Waste Management System in Franklin County, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 56)
  - Valuation of Structured Settlements, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 57)
  - Authorizes the Use of Floridone to Eradicate Aquatic Weed Growth, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 58-59)
  - Vacancy in the Office of the Lieutenant Governor would be Filled by Nominated Person, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 60)
  - Require Representation by a Town or Village Justice on the Commission of Judicial Conduct, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 61)
  - Grant County Court Jurisdiction Over Restitution Actions and Article 78, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 62)
  - Extend Time for Agent Orange Claims, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 63)
  - Terms and Conditions of Employment of Certain Nonjudicial Employees in New York City, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 64)
  - Legislative Resolution, Mourning the death of J. FitzPatrick, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 65)
  - Legislative Resolution, 100th Anniversary of Glens Falls Elks Lodge #81, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 66)
  - Appointment of Law Guardians and Compensation, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 67)
  - Clients' Security Fund, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 68)
  - Insert Procedures to Determine Gubernatorial Inability, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 69)
  - Legislative Resolution, Retirement of S. Silverstein, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 70)
  - Exclude the Town of Saranac from Adirondack Park, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 71)
  - Provide Long Range Planning of Forest Management by the DEC, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 72)
  - Private Right of Action if Employee is Punished for Absence for Jury Duty, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 73)
  - Exclusive Right to Publish the Official Reports, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 74)
  - Give Defendant Twenty Days from Service to Answer the Summons, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 75)
  - Jury Demand Fee, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 76)
  - Court Facilities Incentive Aid, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 77)
  - Excluding Religious Work from Employment Definition for Unemployment Insurance Purposes, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 78)
  - Allow Children to Attend Schools in Other Districts where they Legally Reside without Paying Tuition, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 79)
  - Creating a Common Retirement Fund Board of Trustees, 1988 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 80)
  - Exempting Existing Facilities from Changes, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 81)
  - Adirondack Park Tax District, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 82)
  - Revaluate the Adirondack Private Land Use Classifications and Criteria, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 83)
  - Creation of the New York State Business and Economic Development Act, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 84)
  - Two Year Moratorium on the Destruction of Man-Made Structures in Adirondack Park, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 85)
  - Establishment of Forest Management plan within Adirondack Park, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 86)
  - Clarify that any State-Assisted Not-for-Profit Local Development Corporation is subject to the Freedom of Information Law and Open Meetings Law, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 87)
  - State Assistance for Counties which have created the Office of County Fire Coordinator, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 88)
  - "Forever Wild" Adirondack Park Management, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 89)
  - Preferred Trooper Training, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 90)
  - Designate the Champlain Trail as a Scenic Trail, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 91)
  - Centralized Administration of the Regional Park Police, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 92)
  - Require Representation by a Town or Village Justice on the Commission of Judicial Conduct, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 93)
  - New York State Right of Privacy, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 94)
  - SUNY Division of Security and Law Enforcement, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 95)
  - State Aid to Reimburse Counties for the Salary Increase Mandated for Full Time DAs, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 96)
  - Authorize the Transfer of Maintenance of Certain State Highways to St. Lawrence County, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 97)
  - Transportation for Pupils who face Hazardous Traffic Circumstances, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 98)
  - Reimbursement to Counties for Physics Revaluation of Real Property, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 99)
  - Two Weeks to Obtain Employment Certificates for Minors after Hiring, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 100)
  - Permit Hand Gun Possession During Bow-Hunting Season, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 101)
  - Hand Gun Possession During Competition, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 102)
  - Assist Improvement of Gore Mountain Ski Center Snowmaking, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 103)
  - Land Owner's Liability for Outdoor Sports, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 104)
  - Requirement of Fort Edward's Approval for an Industrial Hazardous Waste Facility within its borders, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 105)
  - Deer Management Unit 39, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 106)
  - Creation of a Hudson Falls/Kingsbury Industrial Development Agency, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 107)
  - Washington County Property Tax Due Date, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 108)
  - Reimburse Washington County Sewer District #2 for Construction Delays, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 109)
  - Fish-for-Free Weekend, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 110)
  - Whitehall Sewage Treatment, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 111)
  - Propane Utility Tax, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 112)
  - Method and Place of Service of Summons, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 113)
  - Reimbursement for County Constructed Sewage Treatment Facilities, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 114)
  - Require Placement of State Funds in Interest Bearing Accounts, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 115)
  - Exempt Alien Agricultural Employers from Unemployment Insurance, 1989 (Box 19 (9-Legislation), Folder 116)
  - Limit State Mandates on School Districts and Local Governments, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 1)
  - Appeal Must be Taken within 30 days after sentencing, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 2)
  - Attorneys Names Transferred to the Court of Appeals and other Appellate Divisions, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 3)
  - Taking and Filing of Oaths of Office, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 4)
  - Unclassified Service in the SUNY System, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - Jury Consideration of Lesser Included Offenses, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - Increase the Maximum Limit for Arbitration Claims, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 7)
  - Elimination of Jury Sequestration Requirements, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 8)
  - Simulcast of Races of Special Interest, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 9)
  - Credit for Teaching in a Military Dependents School Overseas, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - Claim of J. Eiseman, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - Expand the Number of Registrants Allowed in an Election Districts, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - Increase the Annual Budget Cap, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - Authorize the Simulcasting and Betting of Special Races, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - Representative at OTB Hearings, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - Pari-Mutuel Tax Rate Exemptions, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 16)
  - Shift Jurisdictional Responsibility of Some Franklin County Roadways to New York State, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - Tax Credit in Lieu of Medicaid, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 18)
  - Real Property Taxes for Chazy, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - Prohibits Conditioning of Entry into Mobile Home Park Upon Purchase from a Particular Dealer, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - Small Business Exemption from Boiler Inspections, Regulations, and Fees, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - Membership Requirements for Municipality Commissions, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - State Reimbursement for Local Services Home Relief, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - Service of Papers Electronically, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 24)
  - Makes Agricultural Land Exempt from Freshwater Wetlands Act, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 25)
  - Stricter Sanctions Against Juvenile Offenders who have Committed Serious Criminal Acts, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 26)
  - Truck Hoist Licensing Requirements, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 27)
  - Authorize the Creation of the Lake Champlain Economic Development Program, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 28)
  - SUNY Disposal of Lost Property, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 29)
  - Adds a Violation to those Acts Considered Juvenile Delinquency, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 30)
  - Allows Attorneys to Serve Papers to Other Attorneys on Fax Machines, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 31)
  - Interim Term Village Justice for Massena, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 32)
  - Inspection of Racetrack Facilities before Approval of Improvement Fund, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 33)
  - Wetland Designations, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 34)
  - Free Fishing License for the Severely Disabled, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 35)
  - Pari-Mutuel Fringe Benefits, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 36)
  - Identification of All Private Bridges outside of New York City, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 37)
  - Accurately Determine a School's Budget, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 38)
  - Include Heart Conditions as Service Incurred Disabilities for Correctional Officers, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 39)
  - Restore the Person In Need of Supervision (PINS) Age to 18, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 40)
  - Guaranteed Rent from Welfare Tenants and Tenants with Suitable and Inspected Housing, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 41)
  - Homesteads of the Elderly, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 42)
  - Define Emergency Red-Lite, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 43)
  - Exempt Military Service Pensions from New York State Personal Income Tax, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 44)
  - Allows People to Solicit Funds on a State Highway within an Unincorporated Village or Hamlet, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 45)
  - Free Hunting, Fishing, and Big-Game Licenses for the Disabled, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 46)
  - Limit the Time a River is Classified as a "Study", 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 47)
  - Federal Tax Request, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 48)
  - State Highways Stay Open if Town has been Maintaining them, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 49)
  - Youth and Teen Sports Organizations Exemption from Sales Tax, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 50)
  - Purchase of Military Service Credit for Retirement, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 51)
  - Ban Prison Visitors who Introduce Contraband to Correctional Instructions, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 52)
  - State Financial Aid for State Mandated Training Courses at Community Colleges, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 53)
  - Power Authority Retirement Benefits, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 54)
  - Including Route 502 in the State Highway System, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 55)
  - Permits Qualified Psychologists or Psychiatrists to Serve as Trial Psychiatric Examiners, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 56)
  - Credit Rebates for Small Businesses, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 57)
  - Selling 199 Ridge Street to the New York State Association for Retarded Children, Inc. - Warren-Washington Chapter, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 58)
  - Monetary Limit for Refreshments Served at the polls, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 59)
  - Allow a Local Criminal Court to Arraign an Individual Arrested with a Superior Court Bench Warrant if the Judge is Unavailable, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 60)
  - Challenge of Individual Juror, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 61)
  - State Aid for School Buses Purchased by Peru Central School District, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 62)
  - Lay Members of Religious Employment, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 63)
  - Leasing Personal Property, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 64)
  - Unauthorized Use of a Snowmobile, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 65)
  - Management of State Lands within the Adirondack Park, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 66)
  - Handicapped Parking Permits, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 67)
  - Punishment for Operation of a Snowmobile while Intoxicated, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 68)
  - Lighting Districts Assessed by Ad Valorem or Benefit Basis, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 69)
  - Imprisonment Rights to Marry, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 70)
  - Personal Income Tax Deduction for Volunteer Firefighters and Ambulance Squads, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 71)
  - Exclude the Town of Saranac from Adirondack Park, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 72)
  - Remove Fingerprinting Requirement from Handgun License Renewal, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 73)
  - Notice of Hazardous Waste on Property being sold, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 74)
  - Economic Development on Environmental Land, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 75)
  - Unemployment Benefits, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 76)
  - Designation of a Snowmobile as a Motor Vehicle, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 77)
  - Stenographer's Fee, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 78)
  - Worker Compensation Awards, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 79)
  - Exempts Non-Profit Organizations from Environmental Health Inspection Fee, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 80)
  - Retirement Credit to State Police for Local Police Service, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 81)
  - Beer Distributors' Territories, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 82)
  - Saranac Lake Park Lands, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 83)
  - Unlawful Spouse or Heir, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 84)
  - Reconstruction of the Lester Flow Dam, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 85)
  - Provide a New Combination Fishing-Big Game License, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 86)
  - Volunteer Emergency Squad Members Fuel Tax Deduction, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 87)
  - Allow Already Existing Man-Made Structures in the Forest Preserve, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 88)
  - Increase Newspaper Legal Advertising Rates to Meet Inflationary Costs, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 89)
  - Loss of Forest Tax, 1989 (Box 20 (9-Legislation), Folder 90)